{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze D5 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X21i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y3 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee V2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto 1S', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, LED Flash, F2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9500 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels Sony IMX298 + 5 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels Samsung 3L8'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P2140', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.3-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Included'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': '360 N7', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'iOutdoor T1', 'manufacturer': 'ioutdoor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2.0MP HD'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not included'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Philips Swift 4G S626L', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'iOutdoor S950', 'manufacturer': 'ioutdoor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'No rear-mounted camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Included'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV 5800', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas 2 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Philips Xenium X588', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.31 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee BL9000', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5211 Strike', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P211', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.08-megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Philips Xenium S386', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'iOutdoor T2 Walkie-Talkie Phone', 'manufacturer': 'ioutdoor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.3MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not included'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos R2', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '22.57 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'iOutdoor X', 'manufacturer': 'ioutdoor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP+8MP, F/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Philips S327', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom S99', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels + 2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, Sony Exmor RS CMOS Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Konka S5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Konka', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Yun OS 6.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Junior Phone', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic P101', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2560 x 1920 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Philips Xenium V787+', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'VKworld VK7000', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'FinePower C4', 'manufacturer': 'Finepower', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1600 x 1200 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP514', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto Z3 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Assistant AS-5412 max', 'manufacturer': 'Assistant', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'FinePower C2', 'manufacturer': 'Finepower', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Wize Q3', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 2', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1600 x 1200 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic P95', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Assistant AS-501 Club', 'manufacturer': 'Assistant', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'FinePower C1', 'manufacturer': 'Finepower', 'rear_camera': {}, 'front_camera': {}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 3 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn Aura Sleek Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Grace B7', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP401', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga I7', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Hummingbird 3.3 (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Evolveo StrongPhone G8', 'manufacturer': 'Evolveo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG K30', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-treme PQ14', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 3 Power', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Philips Xenium X596', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/2.0 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 6', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Hummingbird 3.3 (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y5 Prime 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo with Emotion 8.0 UI'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M15', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe 7 (Android 7.1.2 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-treme PQ52', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Evolveo StrongPhone G2', 'manufacturer': 'Evolveo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 3', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Life Compact', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 7s', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Magnum X1', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Live L1', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze X5 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-treme PQ51', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Philips Xenium X598', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel f/2.0 + 5 Megapixel with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 5 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-treme PQ26', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV5800 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn Aura Storm', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P2170', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.3-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 15', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 20 Megapixels LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels f/2.0 Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 5', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2560 x 1920 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry KEY2', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.29 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Philips S318', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P1510', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.3-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Included'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Impression ImSmart C551 Ultra Power 6200', 'manufacturer': 'Impression', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Studio View', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y5 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Staari 10', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Philips S395', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y75s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP with LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 5P Lens, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 3.2 (Android 7.1.2 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Impression ImSmart C502 Ultra Power 5000', 'manufacturer': 'Impression', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Kyocera Digno J', 'manufacturer': 'Kyocera', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S9 Active', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'SIRIN LABS FINNEY Blockchain', 'manufacturer': 'SIRIN LABS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo (SIRIN OS)'}
{'device_name': 'Philips S257', 'manufacturer': 'Phillips', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Geecoo Hot1', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot J3', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8MP with AF and Single-LED Flash Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition OS'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 6 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P2160', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia X6', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Impression ImSmart A554 Slim Power 3800', 'manufacturer': 'Impression', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 15 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/1.8 + 20 Megapixels Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels f/2.0 Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi S2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12-Megapixel + 5-Megapixel With PDAF Phase Focus F/2.2 Iris Lens LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16-Megapixel With AI Portrait Mode, Front Single Photo False'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi S2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.2 + 5 Megapixels f/2.0 (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Nova', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP with AF and Single-LED Flash Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Aquaris X2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 6', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Aquaris X2', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Ark Benefit S505', 'manufacturer': 'Ark Elf', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 7 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Lions T1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doov C10', 'manufacturer': 'Doov', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Yun OS 5.1.1 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5701L Slim', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion Z150', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Geotel G9000', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5008L Brave', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 7', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan Nut R1', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP + 20MP Dual Camera with dual high display flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Smartisan OS based on AndroidTM depth customization'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas 1', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao GM-T21', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'VKworld Mix3', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense Infinity F17 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Pixus Volt', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Lanix Ilium Alpha 950 XL', 'manufacturer': 'Lanix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Pixus Raze', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Pixus Pride', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao GM-T11', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-6001L Jumbo', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Impression ImSmart A504 Slim Power 3200', 'manufacturer': 'Impression', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Red Devil', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with CMOS BSI Sensor, 3 element lens, Wide angle lens 76.9°, f2.0 Aperture, 1080p Video'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'OUKITEL K7', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'OS Version: Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Power', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20.16 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lanix Ilium Alpha 950', 'manufacturer': 'Lanix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'QMobile LT100', 'manufacturer': 'QMobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 8', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 720P'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao GM-T51', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Sky', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Impression ImSmart A404 Slim Power 1800', 'manufacturer': 'Impression', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'BLU R1 HD', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao T55', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS (Android 7.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Risio 3', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG V35 ThinQ', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E5 Play MSM8917', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool2', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao 4A', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS (Android 7.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Impression ImSmart C571 Fingerprint', 'manufacturer': 'Impression', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI Z2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E5 Play MSM8920', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos C5S', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Realme 1', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn Titanium Frames S9', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {}, 'front_camera': {}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'InFocus Vision 3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y83', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony Roar V150', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp A2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan Nut Pro 2 Special Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '11.81 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Smartisan 4.2'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Max Pro (M1)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (16MP + 5MP For 6GB Version)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel (16MP 6GB Version) with Face Recognition, 1.0 um Pixel Size, LED Flashlight,'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Konka T1', 'manufacturer': 'Konka', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with LED Flash , CMOS Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Yun OS 6.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y53i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 3.0 OS (Android 6.0.1 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Kult Ambition', 'manufacturer': 'Kult', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar Zumbo Power', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Energy', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG K11', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Kult Impulse', 'manufacturer': 'Kult', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5209L Strike LTE', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Pass', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 10', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 7A Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP with LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Z18 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24MP + 5MP with CMOS sensor, 0.1 seconds focusing speed, F1.7 aperture, and NeoVision 7.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP with AI beauty pre-filling light, F2.0 aperture, and 1.12um large pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1.0'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-6000L Aurora', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'FinePower C3', 'manufacturer': 'Finepower', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Noa N7', 'manufacturer': 'Noa', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels Sony Sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'TP-Link Neffos C7', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5500L Advance', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sonim XP8', 'manufacturer': 'Sonim', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Koolnee K3', 'manufacturer': 'Koolnee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 2MP with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Allview V3 Viper', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Z18 mini', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels, (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, F2,0 Aperture, 1.12 um pixel size, Face recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo with Nubia UI'}
{'device_name': 'TP-Link Neffos C5A', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 6X', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20-Megapixel AI dual'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20-Megapixel "Healing" self-timer'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'AGM X2 SE', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Camera) 1.25 micron Pixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels, 1.029 um pixel size, Samsung S5K3P3 ISOCELL Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao 6P', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Yun OS 5.1.1 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao 7X', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 3 Megapixels, (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Allview P8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ5003L Shark Pro', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'TCL Y660', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'TP-Link Neffos N1', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 86 degree wide angle lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Koolnee Apex', 'manufacturer': 'Koolnee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 2MP with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera with Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y6', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo with Emotion UI 8.0'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx B510 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Allview P7 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao K1', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'FreeMe OS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Power 5', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21MP+5MP with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP + 5MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-4585 Fox View', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao T8+', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow (Yun OS 5.1)'}
{'device_name': 'Allview P9 Life', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx A453 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic P100', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Duo', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Assistant AS-502 Shot', 'manufacturer': 'Assistant', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Nero', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Assistant AS-503 Target', 'manufacturer': 'Assistant', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.4 + 0.3 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Hit Q401 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '640 x 480 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Ark Elf S8', 'manufacturer': 'Ark Elf', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Aquaris VS', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 4P Lens 0.98 µm/pixel Pixel Size, Samsung S5K4H8 CMOS BSI Sensor, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat (Upgradable to Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'NUU Mobile G3', 'manufacturer': 'NUU Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel with Face Recognition, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga Ray 550', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo F8', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Freetel Priori 5', 'manufacturer': 'Freetel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Plum Compass 2', 'manufacturer': 'Plum', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pouvoir 1', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Tiger', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Fun LTE', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Assistant AS-5434 Club', 'manufacturer': 'Assistant', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Freetel Rei 2 Dual', 'manufacturer': 'Freetel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'QMobile S15', 'manufacturer': 'QMobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Aquaris VS Plus', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 4P Lens 0.98 µm/pixel Pixel Size, Samsung S5K4H8 CMOS BSI Sensor, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat (Upgradable to Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP551', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Hammer Titan 2', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'QMobile X36', 'manufacturer': 'QMobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'OS: Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A3', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Geecoo G2', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash, 88 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Eagle 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Senseit T189', 'manufacturer': 'Senseit', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Hurricane', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {}, 'front_camera': {}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 12 MP (f/1.8, 1.25 µm) + 20 MP (f/1.8, 1.0 µm), 2x optical zoom, dual pixel phase detection autofocus, dual-LED dual-tone flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, (f/2.2, 1.0 µm), 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5012L Rich', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Geecoo G6', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with LED Flash, 88 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP510', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Hammer Active', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar Y8 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V9 Youth', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1920 x 1080 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Geecoo G5', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad A1', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Verykool Orion s5204', 'manufacturer': 'Verykool', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 5MP with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP + 2MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Haier G51', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.4 Aperture, Dual-LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Mega 4A', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP550', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'General Mobile GM 8', 'manufacturer': 'General Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Kyocera Basio 3', 'manufacturer': 'Kyocera', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar S11', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels with Face Recognition, 120 Degree Wide Angle Lens #2 Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Sugar OS 3.3 (Android 7.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Haier L8', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5009L Trend', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi A2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels Sony IMX486 (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with Aperture f/2.0, Sony IMX376 Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo (Android One) OS with MIUI 9.5'}
{'device_name': 'Verykool Apollo s5036', 'manufacturer': 'Verykool', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP455', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Kyocera Qua Phone QZ', 'manufacturer': 'Kyocera', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Haier L6', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {}, 'front_camera': {}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5591 Jeans', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Uday', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo EF7', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony P9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Verykool Apollo Quattro s5037', 'manufacturer': 'Verykool', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP+2MP with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP453', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5005L Intense', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo M9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 1.65um Pixel Size, LED Flash, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Haier G8', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat (Upgradable to Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ2 Premium', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Kyocera Digno A', 'manufacturer': 'Kyocera', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V130', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels F/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2 Samsung with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo S3', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A6 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5594 Strike Power Max', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2560 x 1920 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'KEECOO P11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Keecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pop 1', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 7.0 Nougat OS)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A20', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Kyocera DuraForce Pro KC-S702', 'manufacturer': 'Kyocera', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.4 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao Momo', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony P11', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/2.0 Samsung'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Cat S61', 'manufacturer': 'CAT', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo (Upgraded to Android P)'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Start', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5508L Next LTE', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2560 x 1920 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Small Fresh 5s', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 Megapixel With Dual-LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo XL3', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Celkon UniQ', 'manufacturer': 'Celkon', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE A530', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Joy', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i110', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'FinePower C6', 'manufacturer': 'Finepower', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo XL3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 5P Lens, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5007L Iron', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1600 x 1200 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nomi i5730 Infinity', 'manufacturer': 'Nomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels (SW 13MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels (SW 13MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Core 55S', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Verykool Royale Quattro s5702', 'manufacturer': 'Verykool', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP+2MP with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony Roar V78', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2 Samsung'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Celkon CliQ 2', 'manufacturer': 'Celkon', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Koolnee K1 Trio', 'manufacturer': 'Koolnee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'OS Version: Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Core 60S', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5507L Iron Max', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1600 x 1200 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xtouch X10', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Saphir 50X', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo GH7', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Nomi i6030 Note X', 'manufacturer': 'Nomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels (Samsung Sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i70', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion ML245 Electron', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Koolnee Rainbow', 'manufacturer': 'Koolnee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'OS Version: Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5340 Choice', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doov A15s', 'manufacturer': 'Doov', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Yun OS 5.1.1 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Koolnee K5', 'manufacturer': 'Koolnee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-treme PQ34', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2 with 720P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo F7s', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Nomi i5071 Iron-X1', 'manufacturer': 'Nomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion ML450 Super Force', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel (Interpolated 13MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i100', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels Samsung f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doov A19', 'manufacturer': 'Doov', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Yun OS 5.1.1 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'M-Horse Pure 2', 'manufacturer': 'M-Horse', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (13MP Interpolated)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Skin Buffring, Face Lift, Big Eyes, SLR (8MP Interpolated)'}, 'operating_system': 'OS Version: Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo HM4+', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Bravis A506 Crystal', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doov V15', 'manufacturer': 'Doov', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Yun OS 3.2.0 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'Nomi i5001 Evo M3', 'manufacturer': 'Nomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.3 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion G150', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel + 5 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doov V33', 'manufacturer': 'Doov', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion Z255', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nomi i5012 Evo M2', 'manufacturer': 'Nomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Bravis A552 Joy Max', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'Texet TM-5581', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Yezz Andy 5E4', 'manufacturer': 'Yezz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'M-Horse Pure 3', 'manufacturer': 'M-Horse', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'OS Version: Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'TP-Link Neffos Y5s', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Bravis A505 Joy Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'BLU A5 Energy', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nomi i5032 Evo X2', 'manufacturer': 'Nomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion Z155', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nomi i5532 Space X2', 'manufacturer': 'Nomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion X150 Metal', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan Nut 3', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Smartisan 4.x (Android 7.1.2 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP + 16MP with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bolt Q3001', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android, v6 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo S5', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 6', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/1.7 + 5 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/2.0 Aperture, Auto HDR, Gyro EIS, 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A1', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 5P Lens, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 3.2 (Android 7.1.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT70', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/2.8 + 5 MP with the Single-LED flashlight and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel f/2.8 Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C9', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doopro P2', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo R15 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/1.7 + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels f/2.0 with 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo (ColorOS 5.0) OS'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixel f/1.7 + 20 Megapixel f/1.7 + 2 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels f/2.0 Aperture, Autofocus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo (EMUI 8.0) OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG K9', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom S8', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP + 5.0MP Sony with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Max (M1) S425', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP f/2.0 + 8 MP Dual Back cameras with LED Flash, Gyro EIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP f/2.2 Front cameras'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon X', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash, CMOS Sensor, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 3.3 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 3e', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 16+2 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes with Single-LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo with Emotion 8.0 UI'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo Power 5', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP+5MP with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'HOMTOM S9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixel with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.0, 1080p & Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X21', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/1.8 + 5 Megapixels f/2.4 with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixel f/2.0 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Prime 2', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel With AF and LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with F1.9 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13+2 Megapixels f/2.2 with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Face Detection'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo with Emotion UI 8.0 OS'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon X Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash, CMOS Sensor, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 3.3 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Max (M1) S430', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.0 + 8 Megapixel with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V9', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP + 5MP f/2.0 with LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 4.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y9 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP Dual Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP Dual Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS, v8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE ZFive G LTE', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT20', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels Rear Camera With LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow (Color OS )'}
{'device_name': 'iLa Silk', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13+2 Megapixels f/2.0 with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 5P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo One Plus', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo R15', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '22.6MP+13MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS v8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S60 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Samsung S5K4H8YX CMOS Sensor, F2.8 Aperture, 87 Degree Wide Angle Lens, HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 6', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP + 16 MP, f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT16 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P20 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels with Hybrid Zoom, LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn Titanium Jumbo 2', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee X1', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Front camera with 1080P Video Recording'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax X507', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.3 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.3 MP Primary Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT16', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with LED Flash and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with 1600 x 1200 Pixels Image Resolutions'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v6.0 Marshmallow Operating System'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense H11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with Face Detection, f/2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot P20', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K10000 Mix', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Verso', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 megapixels with LED, Digital image stabilization, Touch to focus, Face detection, Digital zoom, Geo tagging'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Itel it5250', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.3 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.3 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Not Available'}
{'device_name': 'AGM X3', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT3', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP Rear Camera With LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes With 5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Hardcase H590S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Single-LED Flash and AF 16MP + 0.3MP Dual Back cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 03MP Dual Front cameras'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S9+ SD845', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, F1.7 Aperture, Laser autofocus, PDAF Focus, Dual Video Call, Auto HDR, Pixel Size 1.22µm, Sensor 1/3.6-inch'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark CM', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP with Quad-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 2.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y7 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 15 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with DualTone LED flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixel Front selfie camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia N3', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP+5MP rear camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Power Max P490S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8MP + 0.3MP with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP + 0.3MP Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 7C', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 13 MP + 2 MP, phase detection autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat Go', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 5 ZE620KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20.2 Megapixels with OmniVision OV8856 PureCel Sensor, F2.0 Aperture, 83 Degree Wide Angle Lens, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Jerry 3', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee M7', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels (SW 16MP) + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 8.1 Oreo) OS'}
{'device_name': 'Moto E5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 8e', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 3 XL', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 5z ZS620KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20.2 Megapixels with OmniVision OV8856 PureCel Sensor, F2.0 Aperture, 83 Degree Wide Angle Lens, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone 5 Lite Snapdragon 430', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/2.2 + Unknown Megapixel (12mm) wide angle with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixel + 20 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 8 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A6 Max', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 OS'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 7A', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with F2.0 Aperture, Face recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U19', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K5 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X50', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel + 0.3 Megapixel f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '18 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J4', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y7 Pro 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with F2.0 Aperture, Face recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Max Plus (M1)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP + 8MP f/2.0 with Single-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels withBeauty Mode, f/2.0 Aperture, 85 ° Wide Angle'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat with ZenUI 4.0'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo R15 Dream Mirror Edition', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 4.0 (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel WP5000', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixel + 5 Megapixel f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nogat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos S3 mini', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doopro P4', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Moto Z3 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 12 MP (f/1.6) + 8 MP, phase detection and laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (f/2.0, 1.4 µm), dual-LED dual-tone flash, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom S16', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Teclast A10S', 'manufacturer': 'Teclast', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Max (M1)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 13 MP (f/2.0) + 8 MP (17mm, no AF), gyro EIS, phase detection autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.2, 25mm), gyro EIS'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Moto Z3', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 12 MP (f/1.6) + 8 MP,'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (f/2.0, 1.4 µm), dual-LED dual-tone flash, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia V18', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A83 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13-megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8-megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom S7', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT26', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Single-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doopro P4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 5z (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 12 MP (f/1.8, 24 mm, 1.4 µm) + Unknown MP (12mm), phase detection autofocus, gyro EIS, dual-LED (dual tone) flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.0, 24mm), 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K9', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z91', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13-megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI A1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Rear camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'UMI OS (Android 8.1 Oreo) OS'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom S12', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel + 2 Megapixel with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung W2018', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP Primary Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y85 (RUMORED)', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 5P Lens, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 4.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu S6', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X21 UD', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/1.8 + 5 Megapixel f/2.4'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.0 with 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 12 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT30', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor View 10', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '(16 Megapixel f/1.8 + 20 Megapixel) with LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Tommy 3', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate RS Porsche Design', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Triple: 40 MP (f/1.8, 1/1.7", OIS) + 20 MP (f/1.6) + 8 MP (f/2.4), Leica optics, 3x optical zoom, phase detection and laser autofocus, dual-LED dual-tone flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP, autofocus, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo D5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels (SW 13MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel (SW 8MP) Sony Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Apex', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 8', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 4', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT27', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Power Max P16K Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View Max', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview P10000 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13-megapixel primary camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5-megapixel front shooter for selfies'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG X4', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 8110 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No Primary Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'KaiOS'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Power Max 490S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8-megapixel primary camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5-megapixel front shooter for selfies'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Infinity Life', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (f/2.0, 1/3", 1.12 µm), autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 (Nougat), planned upgrade to Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP Rear Camera With LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes With 5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F7', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z50', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View Go', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'UmiDigi A1', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13M+2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS v8.1 Oreo (Stock Android)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Aristo', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels With Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U12+ (Plus)', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/1.6 + 16 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels f/2.0, HDR Support'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K5 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn A9 Indian', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Camera 5 MP Primary Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2560 x 1920 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT30 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo XRover', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 0.18 inch Sensor Size, 1.103um Pixel Size, Sony IMX219PQ Exmor R CMOS BSI Sensor,'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone 5 Lite S630', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 20 Megapixel with F2.0 Aperture, Sony Imx376 Exmor RS sensorLED Flashlight'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Roar 5', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel AF and Single-LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Zone 4', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 100 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 5 AI', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.9 +5 MP f/2.0, 1.4 μm with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Sony Lens, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 12', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixel with LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT37', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ2 Compact', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19 Megapixels f/2.0 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2 with 1080P, Gyro EIS'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee Apollo 2', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee V2', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels with Interpolated resolution 13 Megapixels, Face Recognition,LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT17 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with AF and LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.0, 1.12 µm with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone T2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ2', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19 Megapixels f/2.0, 1.22 µm'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2 with 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3X', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.0, + 5 Megapixel f/2.2 with Dual-Tone LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT17', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with 1600 x 1200 Pixels Image Resolutions'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto X4 6GB', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP +8 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with f/2.0 & Pixel size 1.0µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG V30S ThinQ', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/1.6 + 13 Megapixels f/1.9 (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2, 90° Wide Angle Lens, Face Recognition, 1.12 um Pixel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1C', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8MP with LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT37 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG V30S+ ThinQ', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/1.6 + 13 Megapixels f/1.9 (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2, 90° Wide Angle Lens, Face Recognition, 1.12 um Pixel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate SE', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels 1/2.9", 1.25 µm + 2 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Powered Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View 2', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG X300', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels With Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom HT50', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG X Power 2', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Single-LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Tempo Go', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V9 Vita', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera) with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 8 Sirocco', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixel + 13 Megapixel f/1.7 with AF and Dual LED Flash Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Samsung BSI CMOS Sensor, PDAF, 1.4um, f/2.0, 78.4˚, Phase Detection, Display Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S9 Exynos', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/1.5-2.4 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S9 Plus Exynos', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP + 12MP f/1.5-2.4 with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG K20', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG K8 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG K10 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 720P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG K10+ (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP or 8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy On Max', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash, F1.9 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Power 2 American Version', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Leadership 8', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Single LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 Eclipse', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E5', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.0 with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera f/2.0, 1.4 µm with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A85', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 5P Lens, CMOS Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Color OS 3.2 (Android 7.1.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E4 Plus (USA)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.0 with LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel f/2.2 Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone S7', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG K10α (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy C7 (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Nxt', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel with F2.2 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos EA', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi MIX 2 Special Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Omnivision OV5675 Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto X4 (6GB)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP +8 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with f/2.0 & Pixel size 1.0µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone T1 Premium Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (S5K3P3 Sensor)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels (Interpolated to 13.0MP) f/2.0 aperture with Selfie Softlight'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A5 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/1.8 with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/1.8 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Hawkeye', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Camera) with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera with Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Neo', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel with F2.2 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 5T International Version', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 20 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 1.0µm pixel, EIS Sensor, f2.0 Aperture, 1080p Video'}, 'operating_system': 'Oxygen OS Powered (Android 7.1 Nougat) OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 5A Global', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, PDAF Focus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 (2018) USA', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with AF and LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Meiigoo Note 10', 'manufacturer': 'Meiigoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera) f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera) with LED Flash, Face Beauty'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Tiger X', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J2 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8 Active', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash, F1.7 Aperture, Dual Video Call'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V8 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 MP (Dual Camera) LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 720p Video Recoding, Moonlight LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 1', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Jasper LTE', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry Priv', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '18 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v5.1.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 6 International Version', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 aperture,1.12µm sensor,84 degree wide angle lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Folder 2', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Power 3S', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixel with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 5A Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, OmniVision PureCel Sensor, PDAF Focus, 76,4 ° Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K6 Power', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDigi Z Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Samsung S5K3L8 Sensor, 6P Lens, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V8 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 720p Video Recoding, Display Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note 8 MSM8998', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 + 12 Megapixels OIS, 1.55µm pixel size'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F1.7 Aperture,Smart Autofocus,1/3.6-inch Sensor Size,Selective Focus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Y1', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'UmiDIGI C Note', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with GalaxyCore GC5005 Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Acer Liquid Z6E', 'manufacturer': 'Acer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE V870', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Aperture f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note 8 Exynos', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 + 12 Megapixels OIS, 1.55µm pixel size'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F1.7 Aperture,Smart Autofocus,1/3.6-inch Sensor Size,Selective Focus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Y1 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Android One X1', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.4 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F1.9 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor X', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A520', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 5 (China version)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 5P Lens, Pixel Size 1.25μm, PDAF Focus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'UmiDIGI G', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Core', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2, LED Flash, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia M2 Play', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Chuwi HiBook Pro Z8350', 'manufacturer': 'Chuwi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Rear camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Rear camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Microsoft Windows 10, Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDigi Z', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Samsung S5K3L8 Sensor, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Starmobile Up Groove', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Chuwi SurBook', 'manufacturer': 'Chuwi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Microsoft Windows 10 OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V8 (64GB)', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera) with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan Pro 32GB', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 720p Video Recording, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Smartisan OS 3.6 Based on Android OS'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Lenny 4', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos L2', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.1 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 85 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A521', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDIGI Z1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 + 5 Megapixels Samsung S5K3L8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.8'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U7 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDIGI C Note 2', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels, SAMSUNG S5K3L8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels GC5005'}, 'operating_system': 'UMI OS Powered Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C5', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated resolution 5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'VKworld Mix', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 6 B20', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 aperture,1.12µm sensor,84 degree wide angle lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan Pro 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 720p Video Recording, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Smartisan OS 3.7 Based on Android OS'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDIGI S', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels +5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Beauty Mode Selfie'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A612', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M E2', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Quad-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow with Flyme 6.0 UI'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel 10000 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE N939Sc (Blade A711)', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2 with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel 10000 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDIGI C2', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels, Samsung S5K3L8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels GC5005'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 8 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with PDAF, 1.12um, f/2.0, 78.4˚, Display Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade Spark', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Note 5.5', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee Apollo X', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with PDAF Focus, 0.1s Focus, Samsung S5K5E2 Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'XOS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia N1 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with Single-LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan Pro 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 720p Video Recording, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Smartisan OS 3.7 Based on Android OS'}
{'device_name': 'UmiDIGI Crystal Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K10000 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos S2 Higher Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with CMOS sensor, 1.4µm large pixel, 5P Lens, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Lions T1 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'UmiDIGI Crystal MT6737T', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera) Samsung Sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U11 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels (SW 16.0MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels (SW 16.0MP) with 1.019 um Pixel Size, ON Semiconductor AR1335 CMOS Sensor, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee Thor E', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 9', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel + 13 Megapixels Front Facing Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia M2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Blue Filter Glass, 5P Lens, 80 Degree Wide Angle,F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia N2', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 2um Pixel Size, Blue Filter Glass, 5P Lens, 80 Degree Wide Angle,F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J2 Ace', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos S2 Standard Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with CMOS sensor, 1.4µm large pixel, 5P Lens, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U22', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels (SW 13.0MP) + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels (SW 8.0MP) + 2 Megapixels with CMOS Sensor, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI S2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Umi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels Dual Rear camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'UMI OS (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee Mars Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels (Real 8.0MP)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels (Real 2.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone GQ3028', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, OmniVision OV5648 Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Z3', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with F1.8 Aperture, 80.7 Degree Wide Angle Lens, Phase Detection'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Avid 916', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Dual LED flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 Lollipop OS'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp R1', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia M2', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 2um Pixel Size, Blue Filter Glass, 5P Lens, 80 Degree Wide Angle,F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 V', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat with TouchWiz UI'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Gemini', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 + 5 Megapixels Dual Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow Upgradable to Android 7.0 Naught'}
{'device_name': 'LG Rebel 3 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F3 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Aperture F2.0, 5P Lens,1080p Video Recording, Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E4 Plus MT6737', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos R Compact', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 5-element lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Tiger Lite 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel with Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Perx', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A602', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8 G9500', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.2 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Marshmallow Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E4 MT6737', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E4', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone S8', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Amp Prime 2', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos Sense', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Prestige 2', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 6 Global', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with UltraPixel Camera, Sony IMX268 Sensor, Magic Mirror mode, Face Beauty 3.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto Z2 Force', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with Dual LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8 G950F', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.2 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Marshmallow Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 5X Global Version', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels +12 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Magic Mirror,1080p video,Face Beauty 3.0,Real Time Beauty'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Z17 Mini Standard Edition', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels+13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, 5P Lens, F2,0 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos Sense Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi A1 (5X)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash & 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat Upgrade to Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8 Plus G955U', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.2 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Marshmallow Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G5S', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Zmax Champ LTE', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Sol 2', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.3 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp S3', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G5S Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos Sense Basic', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Wide 2 J727S', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8 Plus G955F', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.2 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Marshmallow Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE ZFive L LTE', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G6', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 5 MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp R1S', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.4 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade Max 3', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2,2 Aperture, CMOS Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8 G950K', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.2 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Marshmallow Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note Fan Edition MSM8996', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Samsung S5K4E6 ISOCELL Sensor, 22mm Wide,Dual Video Call,Auto HDR,F1.7 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 5 MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP F/2.0 Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Zmax Grand LTE', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note Fan Edition Exynos', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Samsung S5K4E6 ISOCELL Sensor, 22mm Wide,Dual Video Call,Auto HDR,F1.7 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8 Plus G955K', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.2 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Marshmallow Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Pi', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G6 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel + 5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto X5', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 8 MP f/1.8 with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo, Android One OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 7s', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2,2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with F1.9 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8 Plus G955FD', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.2 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Marshmallow Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Max XL', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, LED Flash, CMOS Sensor,'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Halo', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 (2017) J330', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel With AF and LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu E3', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat (Upgradable to Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Prime (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel With AF and LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy C10 (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels f/1.8 with Dual LED flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front selfie camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 Pro (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A7 2018 (Rumored)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade X Max', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LeTV LeEco Le Pro 3 Elite X722', 'manufacturer': 'LeEco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/2.2 Aperture, 1.4μm Pixel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U18', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels (SW 13.0MP) with 1.127 um Pixel Size, OmniVision OV8856 PureCel CMOS Sensor, 0.18 inch Sensor Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Vdeo 1', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'LG Exalt LTE', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'Proprietary OS'}
{'device_name': 'Lava X28 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash, 84 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U12', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 20MP + 20MP f/1.7, phase detection autofocus, OIS, dual-LED (dual tone) flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS, v7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Zero 5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with LED Flash, CMOS Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Chameleon 3.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG G6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 100 Degree Wide Angle Lens, F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Mega 2 Plus Q426+', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Display Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z25', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Star OS 3.3 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'VKworld Mix 2', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Galaxycore gc5025 Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG G7', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual-camera setup on the back (a standard and a wide-angle lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No Data Available'}, 'operating_system': 'Android, v7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Spark Vdeo Q415', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P20', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '40MP Tri Cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android (8.0)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bolt Q354', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone SE 2', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 7', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee M6', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Interpolated resolution 13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 7.0 Nougat) OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG X Charge', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Uhans I8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 3 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'iNew U7 4G', 'manufacturer': 'iNew', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Tommy 2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Evok Note E453', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z10', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash, F2.2 Aperture, 1.4 micron pixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Star OS 3.3 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Mix 2s', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 12 + 12 MP | f/1.8, 1/2.55" + 1.4 µm f/2.4, 1/2.9", 1.0 µm | dual pixel dual phase detection autofocus, 4-axis OIS, 2x optical zoom'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Evok Power', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Lenny 4 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'VKworld VK7000', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bolt Supreme 4 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q6α', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn Aura Note 2', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'VKworld T2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Sunny 2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'THL Knight 1', 'manufacturer': 'THL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with Interpolated Resolution Up to 13 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 12 MP (f/1.6, 26mm, 1/2.55", 1.4 µm, Dual Pixel PDAF) + 12MP (f/2.4, 52mm, 1/3.6", 1 µm, AF), OIS, phase detection autofocus, 2x optical zoom, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.6, autofocus, 1440p, dual video call, Auto HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Magnus HD Q421', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Robby 2', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 9 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 13 MP (f/2.0, 1.12 µm), phase detection & laser autofocus, Carl Zeiss optics, OIS, dual-LED dual-tone flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 5 MP (f/2.0, AF, 1080p) + 5 MP (f/2.4, no AF)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bolt Pace Q402', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.3 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Spice V801', 'manufacturer': 'Spice', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q6+', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon CM', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 2.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Uhans A6', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn A40 Indian', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Yunique 2', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'iLA D1 Big Eyes', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon I', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, LED Flash, 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 2.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Evok Dual Note', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 +5 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with AF and LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia M2 Lite (NX573J)', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Blue Filter Glass, 5P Lens, 80 Degree Wide Angle,F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'YU Yureka Black', 'manufacturer': 'Yu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 84.3 Degree Wide Angle Lens, LED Flash, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'LG K20', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno W3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn K9 Smart Eco', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'YU Yureka 2', 'manufacturer': 'Yu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat 5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Air', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 2.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'iLA S1 King Kong', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meitu T8', 'manufacturer': 'Meitu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Sony IMX362 Exmor RS CMOS Sensor, Aperture F1.8, 6P Lens, 1.44 um Pixel Size, 1080p Video, Milbeaut Image Processor (Fujitsu), OIS,'}, 'operating_system': 'MEIOS 3.5 OS (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Uhans S3', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Idol 4 Pro Windows Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 1080p Video, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Microsoft Windows 10 OS'}
{'device_name': 'Meitu M8', 'manufacturer': 'Meitu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels SONY IMX362 Exmor RS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with SamSung 2L7 Sensor, 1080p Video,'}, 'operating_system': 'MEIOS 3.5 OS (Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS)'}
{'device_name': 'LG V30 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/1.6 + 13 Megapixels f/1.9 (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2, 90° Wide'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn Titanium Frames S7', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'iLA X', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Maze Blade', 'manufacturer': 'Maze', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 84° Wide Angle Lens, 1.4 µm Pixel Size, Sony IMX 179 Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'UHANS MX', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meitu T8s', 'manufacturer': 'Meitu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels Sony IMX230 Exmor RS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Sony IMX362 Exmor RS CMOS Sensor, Aperture f/1.8, 6P Lens, 1.44 um Pixel Size + 5 Megapixel SAMSUNG 4E8'}, 'operating_system': 'MEIOS 4.0 OS (Android 7.1 Nougat OS)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel U3', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.3 Megapixels with Single LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'InFocus M5s', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 84 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG K8V (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG LS7 4G LTE', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel IdealXCITE', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meitu M8s', 'manufacturer': 'Meitu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels SONY IMX362 Exmor RS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12MP+5MP with Phase Detection, 6P Lens, OIS, SONY IMX230 Exmor RS CMOS Sensor, Aperture f/1.8, 1080p Video,'}, 'operating_system': 'MEIOS 4.0 OS (Android 7.1 Nougat OS)'}
{'device_name': 'UHANS Max 2', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'MAZE Comet', 'manufacturer': 'Maze', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 84 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Meitu V6', 'manufacturer': 'Meitu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12MP+12MP Dual Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'MEIOS 4.0 (Android 7.1 Nougat OS)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel A50', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG X400', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 120 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel XL2', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.3 Megapixels 1.55µm, f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/1.8, 1.4 µm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 OS'}
{'device_name': 'Infocus Turbo 5', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Maze Alpha X', 'manufacturer': 'Maze', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels Sony IMX258'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.0, Sony IMX219'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG Fiesta 2 CDMA', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LYF Water 7S', 'manufacturer': 'LYF', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto Green Pomelo', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with f/2.0 & Pixel size 1.0µm & LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel A30 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Phoenix 3', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'LYF C459', 'manufacturer': 'LYF', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP Camera with Yes, Red Eye Reduction, Smile Detection, Panorama'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP Camera selfie camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel A30 Fierce', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash, 84 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'InFocus A1', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'LG Fortune', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'LG K20 V', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG K10 Power', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash, 120 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel U50', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat, OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG Signature Edition', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/1.6 + 13 Megapixels f/1.9 (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2, 90° Wide, 1.12um Pixel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LYF C451', 'manufacturer': 'LYF', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5MP Primary Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS, v6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo P1', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, LED Flash, 3P Lens, 77.9 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS 3.0 Lite (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG K10 Novo', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 120 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X53', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Infocus Turbo 5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto Z (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Cameras) (RGB + Monochrome)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 85 Degree Wide Angle Lens, Pro Mode, 1.4µm Pixels, OV5695 Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat (Upgradable to Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Risio 2', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Idol 5 Cricket', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with High CRI LED Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X55', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo P1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels +2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 3P Lens, 77.9 Degree Wide Angle Lens, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS 3.0 Lite (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu Pro 7 High Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Infocus Turbo 5s', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Lava X41 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'LG Grace LTE', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel CameoX', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Tribute Dynasty', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG K4 Novo', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'MEIZU MA5', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'InFocus M7s', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 4P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'iNew L7', 'manufacturer': 'iNew', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Lenny 3 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'LG Aristo 2', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels With Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG X500', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel with f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z90', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 8 MP + 2 MP, f/2.0, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo T5c', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels, (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels 3P Lens, 1.12um*1.12um'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'iNew I9', 'manufacturer': 'iNew', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2` Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Nougat Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko U Pulse', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 5T Star Wars Limited Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 20 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 1.0µm pixel, EIS Sensor, f2.0 Aperture, 1080p Video'}, 'operating_system': 'Oxygen OS Powered (Android 7.1 Nougat) OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG Fiesta LTE', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel with f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG Rebel 2 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu A5', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual Camera Set UP (One Front + One Back)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'InFocus A2', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo Z6', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.3 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 2.813um Pixel Size, GalaxyCore GC0409 Sensor, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense Hali', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo Z7', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS 3.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko U Pulse Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A71 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 1.4um Pixel Size, Face Recognition, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo T5s', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels Sony Exmor RS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with AF and LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS 7.0 Powered Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 1.12 micrometer, Auto Focus'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Chameleon 2.2 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense E76 Infinity Elegance', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.4 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu E2 Transformers Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 5P Lens, Exposure compensation, 1.4 µm pixel, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow with Flyme 6.0 UI'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense F26', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 3310 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 1.4um Pixel Size, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Chameleon 2.2 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot S3', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Dual-LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Hummingbird 3.0 (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Wim', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with LED Flash, 1080p video'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Uhans K01', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {}, 'front_camera': {}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Wim Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with LED Flash, 1080p video'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Vdeo 3', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova Lite 2', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo with Emotion UI 8.0 OS'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 4', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 1.4um Pixel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Chameleon 2.2 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Uhans K5000', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Zero 5', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with CMOS Sensr, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Chameleon 3.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot R11', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP, 3P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Jerry Max', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Vdeo 4', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 5 ZE620KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 12 MP (f/1.8, 24 mm, 1/2.55", 1.4 µm, PDAF) + 8 MP (f/2.0, 12 mm, 1/4", 1.12 µm), phase detection autofocus, gyro EIS, dual-LED (dual tone) flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Tommy 2', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Juice A1 Plus Q4260', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bolt Juice Q3551', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Harry', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Vdeo 2', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Jerry 2', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View XL', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad TipTop N1', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Libero 2', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos S3', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/1.8, 1/2.6-inch Senesr Size, 1.4 μm Pixel Size'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.0, 1/3.2 Sensor Size, 1.4-µm Pixel Size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doopro P5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3V', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'ZOPO ZP720', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes With 5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v4.4 KitKat'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo D1', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Max Blue LTE', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview P6', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doopro P3', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Tempo X', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZOPO ZP330', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {}, 'front_camera': {}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BL5000', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Sony IMX362 12MP + Samsung S5K3P9SN 16MP (125° Ultra-wide-angle)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Samsung S5K3P9SP04 16MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 11'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A711', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 88 Degree Wide Angle Selfie'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'AGM STONE 5S', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v4.4.2 KitKat Operating System'}
{'device_name': 'Doopro C1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'ZOPO SPEED 8', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes With 8 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v6.0 Marshmallow Operating System'}
{'device_name': 'Geotel G1 Terminator', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Prime 4G Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Single LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo R1', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Interpolated resolution 13 Megapixels, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'AGM X1', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13+13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense Small Dolphin 2', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doopro P1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color S5', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes With 2 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v5.1 Lollipop up to Marshmallow 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Elyt e1', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash, 3P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BLUBOO S8 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with f/2.8 Aperture, CMOS Sensor, Interpolated resolution 8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': '360 OS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'AGM A2', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense T5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 1.127um Pixel Size, 0.14 inch Sensor Size, F2.4 Aperture, Interpolated Resolution 8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo color C3', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel with AF and LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel with LED Flash, 2P Lens and Aperture F/2.8'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad TipTop N1S', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Zenith 4G Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 2P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense H11', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with Face Detection, f/2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Sky 3 S', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 83.6 Degree Wide Angle Lens, F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color F2', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with AF and Dual-LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel with F/2.8 Aperture, LED Flash, 2P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense Infinity H11', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doopro P5', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': '360 Q5 Plus', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with 1.12um pixel size'}, 'operating_system': '360 2.0 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview S6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Elyt e7', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2, LED Flash, 4P Lens, Hynix Hi-553 CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Power', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense Infinity H11 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color F5', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel with F/2.8 Aperture, LED Flash, 2P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'BLUBOO S8 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 3.0MP Sony Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': '360 Q5', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with 1.12um pixel size'}, 'operating_system': '360 2.0 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS)'}
{'device_name': 'Doopro P2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': '360 F4', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': '360 (Android 5.1 Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua S3', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2, 3P Lens, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S10 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Single LED Flash, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat with Amigo UI'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone C1X', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F/2.8 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Note 5 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Selfie', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel With AF and Single LED Flash Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': '360 F4S', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': '360 2.0 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo D2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP, F2.8 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S50', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Camera) with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZOPO Hero 2', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes With 2 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v6.0 Marshmalow'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A10', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Lions 3', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee BL12000 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels with LED Flash, 88 & 130 Degree Wide Angle Lens,'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Hero C2', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad 5380CA', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color M5', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel with 76.1 Degree Wide Angle'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone Z1', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Power IV', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.4, LED Flash, 3P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee V', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels + 21 Megapixel 21 Megapixels + 21 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color F3', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Aperture F2.8, 2P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Tiptop N2M', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color X5.5i 3G Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.8, 76.1 Degree Wide Angle Lens, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X60L', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Style 3', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone C1 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9000 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Speed X', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with OmniVision OV12830 CMOS BSI 2 Sensor, LED Flash, 5P Lens, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Rainbow 2', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color F1', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Aperture F2.8, 2P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Note', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A1', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview S6', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot R9', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with f/2.8 and LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZOPO Speed 7 (ZP951) Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.2 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes With 5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop OS'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Note Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (SW 16 Megapixels) Sony Sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (SW 16 Megapixels) with 50mA soft flashlight'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone C1', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Flash G5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with 3P Lens, Aperture F2.2, Hynix Hi-553 Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad TipTop Air', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua 5.5 VR+', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Single-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Cloud Style 4G Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A8', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels SW 8.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Blackberry DTEK50', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual Tone LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash, 84˚ wide angle, 1.125um pixel size, f2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot X18', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with 50mA soft flashlight, 5P Lens, Samsung Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color C5', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 2P Lens, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Elyt E6', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot X18 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels (SW 20.0MP) f/2.2+ 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.2 (SW 13.0MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Cloud Q11 4G Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 4P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone H1', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry Neon', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.0 with Dual Tone LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash, 84˚ wide angle'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Defiant', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Note 5', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 80.1 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Amaze+', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Single LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color C5i', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels LED Flash, 2P Lens,F2.8 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone U Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel + 13 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes 8 Megapixel with 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Pegasus 5S', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 aperture, 85 degree wide angle lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua S9 PRO', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ1 Dual', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19 Megapixels f/2.0, 25mm with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel f/2.0, 22mm, 1/3 sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Canvas 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Sky 3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 83.6 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Shoot 2', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee x10', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X20L', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with 86 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X30L', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels with 88 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Young 4G Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels With Aperture F2.8, 3P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Flash X Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Aperture F2.4, 90 Degree Wide Angle Lens, OmniVision OV8865 Sensor, LED Flash, 720p video'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Mega 3', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 83.6 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad M7', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Pegasus 4S Max Plus', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels withBeauty Mode, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat with Zen UI 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Prelude 4G', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X30', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.8, 88 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool S1', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture,OmniVision OV8856 Sensor, Wideangle lens 84°'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool 6', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Pegasus 4S', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels withBeauty Mode, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat with Zen UI 4.1'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Color M4', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X20', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with 86 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Strong 5.1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with 2P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade Vantage', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Fancy Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Splatter', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Hardcase H240S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall Bro', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels, (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'OS Version: Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Z17 Mini High 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels, (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, 5P Lens, F2,0 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Trend Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with F2.4 Aperture, 2P Lens, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Note 5 Lite C', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.4 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy 100', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall T9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels, (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Z17 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Aperture F2.0, 5P Lens, 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, ISOCELL Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Infocus Snap 4', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP + 8 MP with f/2.2 Aperture, 120 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall Rio', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels, (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Torino S2', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Infocus Vision 3', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool Play 6', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Infocus Turbo 5s', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool 1 Dual', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.2, 1.4 µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'Infocus M7S', 'manufacturer': 'Infocus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 4P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool Play 6C', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels with 120 Degree Wide Angle, F2.2 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy On7 Prime (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13.0 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Mega', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, 83.6 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool 1 (C103)', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.2, 1.4 µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo D2', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 8MP, F2.8 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview E7s', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview P2', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview P2 lite', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Unknown', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {}, 'front_camera': {}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Power Max P600S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Power Max P550s', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy S550', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy S500E', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy E20', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy E10', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Hardcase H550S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy E520 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy 400 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.3 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat 2 Q402', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone S8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.0 Megapixel Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel (SW 5.0MP) Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia R1', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS (Upgradeable to Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Evok Note E453', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U11 Life', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, 1080p, HDR, panorama'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo); Android One'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/1.8 + 8 Megapixel with LED-tone flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'AMIGO 5.0 (Android 7.1.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Mix S', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel + 5 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Evok Power Q4260', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Tough Max 2', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with F2.2 Aperture, LED Flash, CMOS Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pulsemix', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 2S', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.0 with Dual LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel f/2.2 Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia R1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS (Upgradeable to Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Avid 4', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel A7 XL', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 12 MP + 2 MP, phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas 2 Q4310', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U11+', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (f/1.7, 1.4 µm, Dual Pixel PDAF), phase detection autofocus, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1080p, HDR, panorama'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone V V520KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP (f/2.0, 1/2.6", 1.0 µm), phase detection & laser autofocus, 4-axis OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1080p, HDR, panorama'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia H8541', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S11S', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/1.8 + 8 Megapixel with LED-tone flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixel + 8 Megapixel Front'}, 'operating_system': 'AMIGO 5.0 (Android 7.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas 1', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.2, 1.4 µm), autofocus, dual-LED dual-tone flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee X', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel + 5 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel + 5 Megapixel Dual'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview P6000', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels + 0.33 Megapixels f/2.0 Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel f/2.0 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Max Plus (M1)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 16 MP (f/2.0, 35mm) + 8 MP (17mm, no AF), phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.0, 25mm)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X9i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel With AF and LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual Camera (20MP + 8MP) Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'FunTouch OS 3.0 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Acer Iconia Talk S', 'manufacturer': 'Acer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, 720p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V9', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 16 MP (f/1.8, 1.12 µm) + 5 MP, phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XA Dual', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (f/2.0, 1/3"), phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (1/4"), autofocus, 1080p, HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow), upgradable to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview S8', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 0.3MP with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel + 0.3 Dual Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y67A', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front camera with Soft Light Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG X4+', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP rear camera with LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP front-facing camera, 100-degree wide-angle lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S11 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel + 2 Megapixel with LED-tone flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'AMIGO 5.0 (Android 7.1 Nougat) OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y79', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/2.0 with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixel f/2.0 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 3.2 Powered Android 7.1.2'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A520C', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Umidigi Z2', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP Dual LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia R1 (Plus)', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, predictive phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, predictive phase detection autofocus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Selfie 2 Q4311', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (f/2.0, 1/3"), autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.0, 1/4"), LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Flash X2', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with GalaxyCore GC5025 CMOS Sensor, F2.2 Aperture, 76.1 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG U', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9000', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels f/2.2 Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel f/2.2 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Xplay 7', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/2.0 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS Powered (Android 7.1.1 Nougat) OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K5', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel with Single-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y65', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2 with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 3.2 Powered Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG K20 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone U', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel + 13 Megapixel Rear Camera with AF & LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y66i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu S30', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Flash X1', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with GalaxyCore GC5025 CMOS Sensor, F2.2 Aperture, 76.1 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Infinity', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (f/2.0, 1/3", 1.12 µm), autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, autofocus, LED flash, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 (Nougat), planned upgrade to Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K10', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP + 0.3MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP + 03MP ( SW 13MP + 8MP ) Dual Front cameras with Single-LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y75', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2 with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/2.0 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 3.2 Powered Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu S30 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo P5000', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Samsung S5K3P3 ISOCELL Sensor, F2.0 Aperture, 1.109um Pxel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LG Harmony', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade Force', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 5', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 12 MP, phase detection autofocus, dual-LED dual-tone flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot KingKong', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Selfie 2 Note Q4601', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (f/2.0, 1/3"), autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.0, 1/4"), LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee P8w', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'VIVO Y53', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu mBlu S6', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android N'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 15', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Z17s', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 23 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels+5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2, 3P Lens, 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall Mix2', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels) f/2.0 CMOS sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3C', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Stylo 3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (1/3", 1.12 µm), autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M6S Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Amigo OS 3.5 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo 5000', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Samsung S5K3P3 ISOCELL Sensor, F2.0 Aperture, 1.109um Pxel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Z17 Mini S', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels+5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2, 5P Lens, 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 15 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel A7', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (f/2.0, 1/3"), phase detection autofocus, dual-LED dual-tone flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U11 Eyes', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall Madrid', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Prelude Plus', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S10B', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels+ 5MP (Dual Camera) with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q8', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 16 MP (28mm, f/1.8, 1/2.6", laser AF, OIS) + 8 MP (10mm, f/2.4, 1/4", no AF), laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (f/1.9, 1/5", 1.12 µm), 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee Elife S8', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Mega Pixel Camera with LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v6.0.1 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee James Bond 2', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S10C', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu MX', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 2.3.5 (Gingerbread), upgradeable to 4.0 (Ice Cream Sandwich)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A6 Premium', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall Atom', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP+2MP with Single-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Idol 5', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (f/2.0, 1/3", 1.12 µm), phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (f/2.4, 1/5", 1.12 µm), 720p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee A1 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 10 Compact', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (f/2.2, 28mm), autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (f/2.8, 34mm)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F106', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Mirror 5s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Allcall Alpha', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels +2MP with Single-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M5', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Mega Pixel Camera with LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P Smart', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 13 MP + 2 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F109L', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V8C', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F109', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo S9', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v7.1 (Nougat) operating system'}
{'device_name': 'Allcall Rio S', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 MP with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'LeEco Le Max 2', 'manufacturer': 'LeEco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP (f/2.0, 1/2.4"), OIS, phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu T10', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'NA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.3MP'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Overture 3', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee W909', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Mega Pixel Camera with LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A39', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (f/2.2, 1/3"), autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (f/2.4, 1/4", 1.4 µm)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat 2+', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F5 Youth', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (f/2.0, 2.0 µm)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone C9', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Sony IMX258 21MP back camera F2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'OV8858 8MP front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee Pioneer P5L', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu T18', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.0 Sony IMX219PC Exmor R Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee X1', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S11', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 16 MP + 5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 16 MP + 8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A330', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A4', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Sony IMX258 13.0 mega pixel back camera F2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'OV8858 8.0 mega pixel front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F6', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels, + 2 MP (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J2 (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone S9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16-megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13-megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M6s', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP camera, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No Data'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee Pioneer P5 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Fanfare 3', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat 3 Q437', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'THL Knight 2', 'manufacturer': 'THL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S5', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone Fighter', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Sony IMX258 13.0 mega pixel back camera F2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'OV8858 8.0 mega pixel front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J2 Pro (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M7 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with LED-flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'AMIGO 5.0 (Android 7.1.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat 4 Q440', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A3', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Sony IMX258 13.0 mega pixel back camera F2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0 mega pixel front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 5', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, (Expected)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual Camera, (16MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone P8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP, up to 4128 x 3096-pixel pictures, HDR, autofocus, Geo-tagging, panorama camera with LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2MP, up to 1600 x 1200-pixel pictures'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.2 KitKat'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Selfie 3 Q460', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F103B', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry DTEK60', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP, f/2.0, phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A2', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Sony IMX258 13.0 mega pixel back camera F2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0 mega pixel front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3V', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, + 2 MP (Dual Cameras)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo), (Expected)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Dual 4 E4816', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 13 MP (f/2.0, 1/3"), autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (1/3")'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone P8 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP with Dual-LED Flash Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F100', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry Keyone', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (f/2.0, 1/2.3", 1.55 µm), phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.2, 1.12 µm), 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 6s', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (f/2.2, 29mm, 1/3", 1.22 µm), phase detection autofocus, dual-LED'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (f/2.2, 31mm), 1080p@30fps, 720p@240fps, face detection, HDR, panorama'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 9, upgradable to iOS 11.2'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu S20', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1X', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat 2 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone P8 3D', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel + 2 Megapixel with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel with Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F306', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop with Amigo UI 3.1'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry Motion', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0, phase detection autofocus, dual-LED'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.2, 1.125 um), 1080p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu M6', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas Infinity Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 20 MP (f/2.0) + 8 MP (f/2.2)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 6s Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (f/2.2, 29mm, 1/3", 1.22 µm), phase detection autofocus, OIS, Dual-LED'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (f/2.2, 31mm), 1080p@30fps, 720p@240fps, face detection, HDR, panorama'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 9, upgradable to iOS 11.2'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone S8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13MP Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F100S', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow with Amigo UI 3.5'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 4 Selfie ZD553KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, 26mm, gyro EIS, phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 20 MP (f/2.0, 31mm) + 8 MP (12mm), LED flash, panorama, HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M6 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel U5 HD', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus,'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Meiigoo Note 8', 'manufacturer': 'Meiigoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP+5 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Acer Liquid Z520', 'manufacturer': 'Acer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.2 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'Meiigoo Mate 10', 'manufacturer': 'Meiigoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Sony 16MP/5MP rear cameras'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13MP/5MP front cameras'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone SE', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (f/2.2, 29mm, 1/3", 1.22 µm), phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.2 MP (f/2.4, 31mm), 720p@30fps, face detection, HDR, FaceTime over Wi-Fi or Cellular'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 9.3.2, upgradable to iOS 11.2'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi R1', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 4 Max ZC520KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 13 MP + 5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, LED'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Dual 5', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 13 MP, phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC One X10', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (f/2.0, 26mm), autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.2, 23mm, 1.12 µm), 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Max 3', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/2.2 with Dual-LED flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel f/2.0 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 4 Max Plus ZC554KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 13 MP + 5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, LED'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Phantom 6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon C9', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS V1.0 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'AGM A8 US Version', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X20', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.8 + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi MIX 2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0 (IMX386)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 7X', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual-cameras: 16MP+2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee Thor E', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels (SW 13.0MP) LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel ( SW 5.0MP ) Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K5000', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels Sony IMX135 with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel (Interpolated 21MP)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'AGM A8 SE', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S9', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 12 MP, f/1.7, 26mm, PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.7, dual video call, Auto HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M6', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Boom J8', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Hi OS (Android 5.1 Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 2', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.2 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee Active', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels Sony Sensor Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 7.0 Nougat OS)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 6 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone S9', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP, f/x.x'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/x.x'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C8 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon C7', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 1.0 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Uhans Note 4', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 2', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO F5', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Little Pepper S11', 'manufacturer': 'Little Pepper', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K10000 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X20 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.8 + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno W4', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 1.0 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'AGM X1 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel With AF and LED Flash Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone S7', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Z17S', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.8 (IMX362) + 23 MP, f/2.0 (IMX318)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP + 5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Uhans Max 2', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K10000 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K320T', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual Rear 8+2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 5', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Mix', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel + 5 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K3', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 + 2 Megapixels with Dual LED flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 + 2 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Z17 miniS', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0 + 5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S60', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo S8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview R6', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Mix 2', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel + 5 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee X1s', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A8+ (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Single 16 Megapixel with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP + 8MP Dual Front Camera with F1.9 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V7', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0 (OV16880)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon CX', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front camera with Dual-LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 2.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Power 3', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels Dual Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon CX Air', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel Front camera with Dual-LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 2.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Meitu T8s', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee MIX 2', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP f/2.0 (IMX 258) + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A3', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP + 2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno L9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Mix 2 Silver', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels f/2.0 Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel + 8 Megapixel f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A75S', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel with LED-flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Color OS 3.2 (Android 7.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A8 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Single 16 Megapixel with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP + 8MP Dual Front Camera with F1.9 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y66', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia L2', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (f/2.0, 1/3.1"), autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (f/2.4, 1/4"), 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S30', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 3 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A75', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel with LED-flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes'}, 'operating_system': 'Color OS 3.2 (Android 7.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q6', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Mix Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy C8', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.7 + 5 MP, f/1.9'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y67', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu S10', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0 (IMX219)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 5T', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP + 16 MP, f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XA2 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP (f/2.0, 24mm, 1/2.3"), phase detection autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 16 MP (f/2.0, 23mm, 1/2.6", OIS, AF) + 8 MP (f/2.4, 1/4")'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee BL12000 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP+13MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP+8MP Dual Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Essential PH-1', 'manufacturer': 'Essential', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (Dual RGB) + 13 MP (Mono), f/1.85'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan Nut Pro 2', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Dula-LED and AF Dual'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Smartisan OS 4.0 Based on Android OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A83', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel with LED-flash Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu S10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Nomu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0 (IMX219)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XA2', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP (f/2.0, 24mm, 1/2.3"), phase detection autofocus, LED flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual: 16 MP (f/2.0, 23mm, 1/2.6", OIS, AF) + 8 MP (f/2.4, 1/4")'}, 'operating_system': 'Google Android™ O'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 7s', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13+2 Megapixels with LED and AF Dual'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo with Emotion UI'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee BL12000', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP+13MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16MP+8MP Dual Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo S8', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Xplay 3S', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.3 (Kitkat)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Mix 2', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels f/2.0 Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel + 8 Megapixel f/2.2 Front camera with Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X20 Plus UD', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.8 + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'AGM A7', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': '360 N6 Lite', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': '360 3.0 (Android 7.1.1 Nougat) OS'}
{'device_name': 'Acer Liquid Z6 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Acer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': '360 N6', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, CMOS Sensor'}, 'operating_system': '360 3.0 (Android 7.1.1 Nougat) OS'}
{'device_name': 'AGM A8 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S10', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP + 8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Tab 4 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon M', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP. f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo M9', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8MP+2MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP+2MP Dual Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS 3.0 Lite (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V5S', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': '360 N6 Pro', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP+2MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': '360 2.0 (Android 7.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'AGM X2', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Camera) with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI S2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16+15MP Dual Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13+15MP Dual Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K8000', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Honor View 10', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual-cameras: 16MP+2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno I3', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Quad LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED & Screen Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo KIICAA Power', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot H3', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP & 3 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20MP, f/2.0 (IMX376) + 8MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 9 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 2MP | 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'VKWorld S8', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Tab 4', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Acer Liquid Z6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Acer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels Rear Camera With Dual-LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo M7', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel with Single-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 2.0 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO A79', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno W3 LTE Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.0 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo M5 Edge', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS 6.0(Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO R11S', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/1.7 + 16 MP, f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 10', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP + 12 MP, f/1.6 (Both), w/ OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M7', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HP Pro 8', 'manufacturer': 'HP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.3 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 6 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/2.0 with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel f/2.0 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO R11S Plus', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/1.7 + 16 MP, f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': '360 F5', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': '360 2.0 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone S8', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixel f/1.8 Sony Rear Camera with AF & LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (Mono) + 12 MP (RGB), f/1.6 (w/ OIS)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Hisense A2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 2S', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 20 MP f/1.8 with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP + 2 MP f/2.0 Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0 (OV16880)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Razer Phone', 'manufacturer': 'Razer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.75 + 12 MP f/2.6'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor V10', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual-cameras: 16MP+2MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 5A', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A6', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M7 Power', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel with AF and LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Honor V9 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone P9000', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP Rear Camera With LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android v6.0 Marshmallow OS'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS Zenfone V', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 2 XL', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.2 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan U2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0 (x2)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.2 (Kitkat), Current: Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee M5', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'AGM X2 Max', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels+21 Megapixels with Dual-LED flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade X', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixel With AF and Single-LED Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO F3', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0 + 8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K8', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee Thor Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'AGM A1Q', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO A77', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K8 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 5', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan U1', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.2 (Kitkat), Current: Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'iOutdoor T1', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K8 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 2', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan T2', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Yu Yureka 2', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI S2', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (IMX258) + 5 MP f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow) | Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 7', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Dual-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat (Upgradable Up to Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan T1', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.2 (Kitkat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG V10', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP + 5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K6', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel + 2 Megapixels with Dual-LED Flash and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel + 2 Megapixel Dual'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO A71', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Honor 6A', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone X', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.8 + 12 MP, f/2.4'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7 MP f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A2S', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 8 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.8 + 12 MP, f/2.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Gemini Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (RGB) + 13 MP (Mono), f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel Mix 2', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP+2MP with Dual-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'AGM X2', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone 8', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7 MP f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 11'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi A1', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/2.2 + 12 MP f/2.6'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Meiigoo S8', 'manufacturer': 'Meiigoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP f/2.2 + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 10 Lite (Maimang 6)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0 + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Notebook Pro 15.6″ (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Windows 10 (Home Version)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Xplay', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.2 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Note 3', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.6 (Telephoto) + 12 MP, f/1.8 (Wide-Angle Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS ZenFone 4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 12 MP f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo S1', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 3 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP + 0.3 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M5c', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Z4', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Tizen 3.0'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 8', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (RGB) + 13 MP (Mono)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (Front)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG V30', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.6 + 13 MP, f/1.9'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Moto Z2 Force', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (Mono) + 12 MP (RGB), f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A7', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP (S5K4E2), f/2.4 + 0.3 MP (GC0310), f/2.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP (GC2385)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS ZenPad Z8 (ZT581KL)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'VKWorld Mix Plus', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pixi 3 (8) LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Microsoft Windows 10'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Pegasus 3', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO R11 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/2.6 + 16 MP, f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone T1', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP f/2.0 (S5K3P3) + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Maze Alpha', 'manufacturer': 'Maze', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP f/2.2 + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pixi 4 (6)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO R11', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 20 MP (f/2.6, AF) + 16 MP (f/1.7, PDAF), phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Magic', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP f/2.4 + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackberry Aurora', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A8', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (IMX149)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y7 Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo T5', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 7 (Chang Xiang 7)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (RGB), f/x.x'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/x.x'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pixi 4 (6) 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo KIICAA Mix', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 216', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pixi 4 (7)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3 ZE520KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, laser/phase detection autofocus, OIS (4-axis)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow), upgradable to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Meiigoo M1', 'manufacturer': 'Meiigoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 8MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 150', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 2', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12MP + 8 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'OUKITEL K6000 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (RGB) f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Fierce XL (Windows)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Microsoft Windows 10'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 230 Dual SIM', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, 480p, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Note 2 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP (RGB) f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U16 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV6000s', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0 (IMX219)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP (OV2680)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto Z2 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7, phase detection and laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0, 1.4 µm pixel size, dual-LED (dual tone) flash, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 230', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, 480p, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo S8', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (Rear) +'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Idol 4', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, 1080p, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X9S Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Primary 16 MP f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Secondary 20 MP & 5 MP f/2.0 (w/ LED Flash)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3 Laser ZC551KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow), upgradable to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV7000 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI Crystal', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP + 2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 6 (2014)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.2 (Kitkat), 5.1.1 (Lollipop), Possible Upgrade 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 222 Dual SIM', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Idol 4s', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, 1080p, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X9S', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Primary 16 MP f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Secondary 20 MP & 5 MP f/2.0 (w/ LED Flash)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 222', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV7000', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'VKWorld S3', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Moto E4 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (NA) | Android 7.1.1 (Intl.)'}
{'device_name': 'LG X venture', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note FE', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7, 26mm, PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.7, 22mm, dual video call'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Go ZB452KG', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP or 8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA, f/2.8 or 2 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'VKWorld T2', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Z11', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.4, 1.4 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia L1', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, 24 mm, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV4000', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0 + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3 Max ZC520TL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 2017', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.7, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, LED flash, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Moto E4', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (NA) | Android 7.1.1 (Intl.)'}
{'device_name': '360 N5S', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, F / 2.0 aperture, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, PDAF , 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'VKWorld F2', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP (Sony IMX149)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J5 2017', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.7, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Hisense H10', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (RGB) f/x.x'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/x.x'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung J7+', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.7 + 5 MP, f/1.9'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 215 Dual Sim', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'YotaPhone 3', 'manufacturer': 'Yotaphone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO A77 (MT Edition)', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Idol 4s Windows', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, 1080p, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Microsoft Windows 10'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI S2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto C Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.8, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Moto G5S Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (RGB) f/x.x'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/x.x'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone P8', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP (Sony IMX230)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (Samsung S5K3P3)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U11', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7, phase detection autofocus, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 215', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto C', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Notebook Air 13.3″ (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Windows 10 (Chinese Version)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone P8 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (Samsung S5K3P3)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS ZenFone 4 Max', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP f/2.0 + ? MP (Wide-angle) f/x.x'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pop 4', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 105 2015', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Moto G5S', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS ZenPad 3S 10 (Z500M)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y69', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone C1 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Max 2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenPad Z10 (ZT500KL)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'OUKITEL K3', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP + 2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 105 Dual SIM 2015', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pop 4 plus', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee BL5000', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP f/2.2 (x2)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note 8', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7 + 12 MP, f/2.4'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.7'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'YotaPhone 2', 'manufacturer': 'Yotaphone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2.1 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos S2', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 8 MP, f/1.75'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3 Deluxe 5.5 ZS550KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, laser/phase detection autofocus, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow), upgradable to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Z17', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.8 + 23 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos R', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '22.6 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16.3 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool M7', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pop 4S', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Pro (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Leader 8', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Moto X4', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0 + 8 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3 Max ZC553KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, phase detection & laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone S8', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP, f/x.x'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/x.x'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.7, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Go ZB450KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M6 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.9 + 5 MP f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel POP 7 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS Zenfone Go (ZB551KL)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP or 13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV8000 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 5', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (Telephoto) f/2.6 + 16 MP (Wide-angle) f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu E2', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1.4 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS Zenfone Go (T500)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Go ZB500KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Redmi Note 5A (S)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Max ZC550KL 2016', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Idol 5S', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 5X', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/2.2 + 12 MP f/2.6'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 9', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP (Mono) + 12 MP (RGB), f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Redmi Note 5A', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS ZenPad 3S 10 LTE (Z500KL)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ1 Compact', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3 ZE552KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, laser/phase detection autofocus, OIS (4-axis)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow), upgradable to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu Pro 7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Primary 12 MP (Mono) f/2.0 + 12 MP (RGB) f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS ZenFone Go (ZC451TG)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.3 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'LeEco Le Max', 'manufacturer': 'LeEco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 MP, f/2.0, autofocus, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP, f/2.0, 1/3" sensor size, 2µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee BL7000', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (x2)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP + 8 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3 Deluxe ZS570KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP, f/2.0, laser/phase detection autofocus, OIS (4-axis)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu Pro 7', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Primary 12 MP (Mono) f/2.0 + 12 MP (RGB) f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LeEco Le 1s', 'manufacturer': 'LeEco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop) - LeEco Le 1s | Android 6.0 (Marshmallow) - LeEco Le 1s Eco'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Go ZB552KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ1', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS Live (G500TG)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Mix', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP f/2.2 + 8MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XA1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS ZenFone 4 Selfie Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (x2) f/1.8'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Flash 2017', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 8 MP + 5 MP, f/2.0, autofocus, dual-LED (dual tone) flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 2 Laser ZE551KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3 Ultra ZU680KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP, f/2.0, laser/phase detection autofocus, OIS (4-axis)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pixi First', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 4.4.2 (KitKat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Fierce 4', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'ASUS ZenFone 4 (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP f/1.8 + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Zoom ZX551ML', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.7-4.8, 28-84mm (3x optical zoom), laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Z17 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (RGB) f/2.2 + 13 MP (Monochrome) - IMX258 Sensors'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Idol 3C', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel X1', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0, 1/4" sensor size, 1.4 µm pixel size, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Flash 2', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Go ZC500TG', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pixi 4 (5)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Max ZC550KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0.1 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Fierce XL', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pop 3 (5)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP or 8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP/ 2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pop 3 (5.5)', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP | 8 MP | 13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP | 5 MP | 8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ Premium', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19 MP, f/2.0, 25mm, EIS (gyro), predictive phase detection and laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 22mm, 1/3" sensor size, 1.12 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia N2', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, F2.2 , PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, F2.0, 5-piece lens, Super beauty skin 2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto M', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, 1/4" sensor size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG K8 2017', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZs', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19 MP, f/2.0, 25mm, EIS (gyro), predictive phase detection and laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 22mm, 1/3" sensor size, 1.12 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F5', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Flash Plus 2', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC One M9s', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, OIS, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP, f/2.0, 27mm, 1/3" sensor size, 2µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M6', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1/4" sensor size, 1.12 µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 828 dual sim', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP, f/2.0, 27mm, 1/3" sensor size, 2µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 6', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (Telephoto) + 12 MP (Wide-Angle Lens)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G5', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.8, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1/4" sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S7 active', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7, 26mm, PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.7, 22mm, dual video call'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow), upgradable to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG K10 2017', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Moto G4 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, phase detection & laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, auto-HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow), planned upgrade to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LeEco Le Pro3 Elite', 'manufacturer': 'LeEco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1.4 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 728 dual sim', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8, 34mm, 1080p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A57', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P8 Lite (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC One E9s dual sim', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP, f/2.0, 27mm, 1/3" sensor size, 2µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'LeEco Le Pro 3 AI', 'manufacturer': 'LeEco', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP, f/2.0, phase detection and laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 1.4 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee P8 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 630', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.4, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Xcover 3 G389F', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto G5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S6s', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor V9', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 12 Mp + 12 MP, F/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, F/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Huawei EMUI 5.0 (compatible with Android 7.0)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J Max', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo M8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Express Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V8', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP + 2MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7, 26mm, PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.7, dual video call, Auto HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Tab J', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 4X', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A3 2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 825', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A5 (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, 27mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Grand Prime Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M5S', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC ONE ME（M9et）', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20.0MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A5 2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, 28mm, OIS, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.9, 24mm, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 526', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, 720p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A3 2017', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 3310 (2017)', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'NIL'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'HTC 10 Lifestyle', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.8, 26mm, OIS, laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.8, 23mm,'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow), upgradable to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F103 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A7 2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, 28mm, OIS, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.9, 24mm, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenPad 3 8.0 (Z581K)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG K3', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 626s', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, 720p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9 2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, 28mm, OIS, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9, 24mm, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC One S9', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, OIS, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP, f/2.0, 27mm, 1/3" sensor size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG K5', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.8'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 5', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1.12 µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Pegasus 3s', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A7 2017', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, 27mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS, v6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee P7 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J1 2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Stylo 2', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 1080p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC One M9 Prime Camera', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, OIS, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP, f/2.0, 27mm, 1/3" sensor size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy C7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J1 Nxt', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Go ZB690KG', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP or 8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 3', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 Emerge', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.9'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S9', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP + 5MP, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S7 USA', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7, 26mm, PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.7, 22mm, dual video call, Auto HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow), upgradable to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 626 USA', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 720p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 628', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4, 28mm, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3 Zoom ZE553KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 12 MP, (25mm, f/1.7, OIS (4-axis) & 59mm, f/2.8), 2.3x zoom, laser/phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 1/3" sensor size, 1.12 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S7 edge USA', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7, 26mm, PDAF, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.7, 22mm, dual video call, Auto HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J1 mini prime', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'VGA'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop) - 3G model | Android 6.0 (Marshmallow) - LTE model'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee P7', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG X style', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 720p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG G6', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP (f/1.8, OIS, 3-axis) + 13 MP (f/2.4), laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia M2', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP + 13 MP, F2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, F2.0, 80 degrees wide angle'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone AR ZS571KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP, f/2.0, OIS (4-axis), 3x zoom, depth & motion tracking sensors, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': '360 N5', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android, 6.0 ( Marshmallow )'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Pixi 4 Plus Power', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED'}, 'operating_system': 'Android'}
{'device_name': 'HTC One A9s', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8, 33.7 mm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J5 2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, 28mm, autofocus,'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.9, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P10 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP + 12 MP, f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V5 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 6', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 1.12 µm pixel size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG X power', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus | 8 MP, autofocus, - LS755, US610, K450'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.4, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/1.9, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Shine Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y55s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P10', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 20 MP + 12 MP, f/2.2, OIS, Leica optics, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9 Pro (2016)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, autofocus, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'OPPO F3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0 + 8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Holly 2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 10 Lifestyle', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8, 34mm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG G Pad X 8.0', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee A1', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Pad 3', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy C5', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG G Pad III 8.0 FHD', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 5c', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/2.2, 27mm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, 27mm, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee A1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP + 5 MP, f/2.0, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 MP, f/2.0, 1/2.8" sensor size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P9 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy C7', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel A3 XL', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 720p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 650', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8, 34mm'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee Steel 2', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG X Mach', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.3 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Tab S3 9.7', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, 27mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, 23mm, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia Z17 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 13 MP, F/2.2 + 13 MP (Monochrome), MX258 RGB Sensor + IMX258 Mono Sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y5II', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'LG X power2', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 1.12 µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG X max', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel A3', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC 10 Evo', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, OIS,PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.4, 1080p, Auto-HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S8+', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.7, 26mm, PDAf, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.7, autofocus, 1440p@30fps, dual video call, Auto HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y3II', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Xcover 4', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel A5 LED', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Butterfly 3', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20.2 MP Duo, f/2.2, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, 2160p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop), planned upgrade to 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG X5', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 5C', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone 3s Max ZC521TL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot CHEETAH 2', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP ( 16.0MP ) with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP ( 13.0MP )'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee Apollo', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21.0MP with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'LG X Skin', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor V8', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 12 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.4'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 5A', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'UMI Plus E', 'manufacturer': 'Umi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP with flash light and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'UMi Z', 'manufacturer': 'Umi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP,with flash light'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0'}
{'device_name': 'Asus Zenfone Live ZB501KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, 1.4 µm pixel size, autofocus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC One A9', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, autofocus, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4 MP, f/2.0, 27mm, 1/3" sensor size, 2µm pixel size, 1080p@30fps, HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow), upgradable to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Nubia M2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, F2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, F2.0, 80 degrees wide angle, Super beauty skin 2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel U5', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U Play', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, OIS, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, 27mm, 1 µm pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei G9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, OIS, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG G Pad III 10.1 FHD', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 4X', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP, f/1.8, 26mm, OIS, laser & PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, 1080p, Auto-HDR'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 2016', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.2, autofocus, - J3109, J320F | 5 MP, f/2.2, autofocus, - J320P, J320A,'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, 720p@30fps - J3109, J320F | 2 MP - J320P, J320A'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee M2017', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Dual 12 MP + 13 MP, 2x optical zoom, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia X Compact', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP, f/2.0, 24mm, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow), planned upgrade to 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, OIS, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'LG K3 2017', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XA1', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP, f/2.0, 24mm, phase detection and laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 23mm, autofocus, 1/4" sensor size, 1080p'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Tab E 8.0', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop), upgradable to 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy C5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.9'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XA1 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23 MP, f/2.0, 24mm, phase detection and laser autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/2.0, 23mm, 1/2.6" sensor size, OIS, autofocus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'LG K4 2017', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Tab A 10.1 (2016)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/1.9, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.2, 1080p video'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee Marathon M5 mini', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Stylus 3', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 (Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Tab A 7.0 (2016)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP, f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S8', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP, f/1.8, PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, 1/4" sensor size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee P5 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.0 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 728 Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.2, 28mm, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8, 34mm, 1080p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1.1 (Lollipop)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 530', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.4, autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee S6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0,PDAF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0.1 (Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC One X9', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0, 28mm, autofocus, OIS'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.8, 34mm, 1080p@30fps'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 (Marshmallow)'}
